<text>
---1.17.2014
    Hey, Kiira fans! Ready for some excitement? Kiira has lately got up to 10 musicians working to make music for the upcoming Kiira Engine! And so far, one artist. Now, I better give you some information on this topic, because it will probably confuse you a little at first.
    Well, in the Kiira Engine there will be libraries of music, art, etc. That can be used for making games, software, and apps. The people who upload to these libraries can do it for free, and they can also have people pay for their resources. The will be a tab off to the side that will allow people to search through each library and load it up as a "variable object" node, to plug into whatever other node they're using in their projects. For instance, if a person wants to create a game and needs a 3D model for a character that they want plugged into a map or assigned as the object a camera follows, they can just drag connectors to it and there you go. From inside the editor nodes (i.e. game editor node) you can manipulate each object in different ways.
    If you would like to view the sandbox just email me and I'll send you a link of what I've got so far.
    Hello, everyone! Ten days into this new year and I'm back here to give you some update on information about the website. :) First things first, the Kiira Engine. I was looking over the code for ThreeNodes.js and it is some very well programmed stuff there... But I didn't particularly like it in terms of using it as something to work off of to create my own code editor. It's useful and it looks pretty, but it doesn't have the simplicity I'm looking for. I want to make the Kiira Engine simple for you guys, so I decided that I'm going to start from scratch using my own code.
---1.10.2014
    I put some thought into how I was going to program in all the features I wanted to, and I'll have you all know that with the way it's programmed, it's completely possible to make your own plugins for it. All nodes in the engine consist of these things: the plugin Javascript (contains all the functions of the plugin, including input and output), the plugin CSS (contains the appearance of the plugin), and the plugin icon (pretty self explanatory). So, making a plugin will be a piece of Cake. And no worries, you'll all have access to that functionality! Kiira, out!
---12.25.2013
    Well, this morning, before I went to bed I made some updates to the website. Tonight, I'm going to be changing quite a lot, all starting with the homepage. Also, I found the source of what I'm going to be using to make the code editor. I might actually contact the person who made the source and ask them if they'd like my help to program more for it, since it's such a great idea. :) Here's the link.It already implements Webgl using the Three.js library. Check for more updates on

---12.25.2013
    Hey, everyone! :) Tonight I've only done small uploads to the website. The Vulcan game page no has the capability to comment and read the description for the game. Mainly, I've been working on the two things I'm adding in for you, the community. I haven't been keeping you up to date with the status of the Kiira Editor and I'll tell you why in just a moment, but let me focus your attention on another matter that's been getting me thinking for nearly a year now.
    Now, I'm sure you've all seen game engines that have drag and drop coding inside of them, right? For instance: Construct 2, Game Maker, and UDK. Those are my top three right there. Each one has a visual code editor. Instead of writing lines of code, you drag and drop things or something like that. All you do is click. Now, lately, I've been sucked into the world of UDK (Unreal Development Kit) programming, and I very much like the Kismet code editor inside of it. But... there is one problem with all of these engines. Wouldn't it be easier if you could use it for other purposes other than a game? Now, I know that I say sometimes that you can make different things using these game engines, but they're not really useful for most other things.
    So, with all of this considered, can you see where I'm getting at? A visual code editor. From here on out, I'm going to start programming a code editor that will be implemented into my website that will be plugin based. I will not upload it right away, but I will when it's in beta form. Now, allow me to elaborate on my plans for this.
    In most programming languages, there are a lot of very similar things. The code editor will be designed to port to multiple different languages. But, the choice of the language will be made at the beginning. Since it's plugin based, some things may only be compatible with certain languages. Though, I figured that this would be a nice way to do something for you guys that I was thinking would be a really nice and creative thing to do, and that's make it so that you can actually add in things like a "Game" plugin and edit variables and things by branching things off of it.You'll see what I'm aiming for when it's in beta stage, but for now, I'm going to keep my mouth shut about it.
    You will be seeing minor updates, because I just don't have the heart to leave you guys on your own, so don't worry. they just won't be as big as they normally are. These are big plans, and will take a lot of work.

---12.21.2013
    Well, I'm uploading again, guys. :) I just got done uploading v1.1 of the Vulcan beta. There is still a lot to do with it, but I've fixed quite a few things. I hope you like it! I will get back to you soon!

---12.18.2013
    Something with Newgrounds prevented me from updating the version of Vulcan that I had published on there so I have temporarily removed the game from the website. I will be re-uploading it this weekend. :) Sorry for the inconvenience.

---12.16.2013
    It's really hard to believe it's almost been 14 days since I last made an update to the website. I've been studying a lot to further my knowledge of programming, so I'm very sorry to all of you who have been coming on here expecting something more than what I have, but I will give you guys a bit of relaxation by releasing the beta for my game Vulcan. Soon, I'm going to be buying a full license to Construct to and releasing that pretty looking game in the slideshow, Vit of Finding Colors. I've been working on Vit for quite a while, and I think you guys might like it. :) I'm going to release the beta with only the map editor included, then make levels afterwords that will include artwork made my yours truly. I hope you all enjoy! I'll get back to you soon. Also, I'm going to start a side project known as the Kiira Innovation Revolution. It will be a community for programmers that support innovation through teamwork. :) That's all I'm going to leave you with on that one, it will take some years to accomplish. Also, I'm working on packages for those who'd like some royalty free downloads, included music and the RPG Collection, which will catre towards those interested in designing an RPG Games like the ones seen in RPG Maker.
    I really do enjoy making those things, so I hope you all enjoy using them! :)
    Lastly, I will leave you with a little tidbit of information on the app: Manga Jutsu. As of right now, I'm currently programming it. Balancing my time out in order to do everything I've told you I'm doing, it's beginning to add some lag to production. Manga Jutsu is scheduled to be finished by the end of next year though, but it might be finished before then. It will be uploaded when it's in beta stage.
    Now, before I get to work on other things, I will release the beta for Vulcan.

---12.2.2013
    Another week, another venture. :) I've uploaded more videos in the Construct 2 tutorial series, and I'm going to keep going until we've built three games together using the program. I hope you all enjoy what I'm doing with that.
    This week I'm going to be working mainly on programming an HTML5 app called Manga Jutsu and working more on my game, Vulcan. Vit, as you see in my slideshow up at the top of the page will be my next project, and I will be working on making that game a reality. :) I hope that you all like what I make for you. Remember, as long as Kiira exists, it will always be here for you. No matter how much work it takes out of me to entertain you, teach you, or supply you with resources, I will be here to make it happen. Kiira is for innovation in all forms of technology and art.
    Also, to anyone wanting to see the project announced a couple months ago known  as InfectionZ, we are currently hiring artists that will be able to work with us. We will be announcing the release of the beta some time next year, but don't tell anyone I told you. ;) It's a secret!

---11.24.2013
    I've been dealing with some issues with the website, but I just got done 4 lessons on Construct 2 yesterday, for beginners. I'm going to go on and make videos over all sorts of things in Construct 2 or just game design in general using it. I'll guide you through steps in making your own games. :) Then, I'm going to go and make Construct tutorials. Construct is just like Construct 2, the only difference is that Construct can build applications for Windows and Direct X9 games, so it's going to be a useful tool for anyone looking to make a game, or an application. It's a really useful tool, but I'll tell you more on that later.

---11.22.2013
    Well, everybody, it's finally Friday! :D I'm really excited to see who all I can help with my Construct 2 tutorials that I'm going to be making this weekend! I'm going to make a couple, all going over different parts of Construct 2, and I'll even show you how I'm making the game: Vulcan, which I'm hoping to wrap up this weekend as well! I hope you like all that I'm going to be giving out! Also, I'm going to be organizing things on the website differently again, I'm getting tired of the cluttered navigation. I'll get back to you soon! Later, everybody!

---11.19.2013
    I'm going to be making a class that goes over everything in Construct 2 in the next couple days. :) I hope you guys like it. I'm going to put a lot of work in that class. Since there's a lot of support for HTML5 games and many people wanting to make an HTML5 game, I figured I would help that group of game designers out.
    After I get done with this, I'm going to try to get some art section on here. See you guys later!

---11.18.2013
    Made some more updates tonight and I've recently uploaded a learning section about designing a platformer, and soon I will be uploading some about other game types.

--- 11.15.2013
    Making some updates tonight while working on the soundtrack for Vulcan. If nybody wants to play it, it should be online by the end of next week. I will be uploading it to Newgrounds.com and then embedding it on my website. I hope you guys enjoy it. :) Also, to all game designers, I will most likely be posting a small Construct 2 project of it that will contain everything, but stripped down, so you can make a game similar to it.

--- 11.14.2013
    Well, I just added to the Creativity in Game Design page on the learn section. I'm going to be changing it up a little from here and there to find out how to best organize everything. I hope you like this new page, everybody, I'll be getting back to you soon. :)

--- 11.13.2013
    Guys, seriously, I have to thank you. :) This past week, the amount of visitors on my site has gone up quite significantly. It's an honor to know that so many people have enjoyed my website and have came back to look at it. As my main goal is to help people in their learning process of designing video games, it's a big win whenever people return to learn more. I feel like I'm succeeding.
    Anyways, I know that I'm getting ready for a competition right now, but I don't want to leave anyone hanging. I'm making another course this week that goes over the significance of creativity in game designing and how you can be creative and come up with new ideas. This is for an audience that already has knowledge of game design.
    Also, in most of my projects I'm going to be using music that Matthew Pablo has made and given me permission to use. Below the slide show is a song he made, you should check it out. He's a very good musician, and his music will be helping my projects out a lot.

--- 11.12.2013
   Sorry to leave you guys hangin! It's a new week and another week closer to the deadline of the Tizen App Competition. Unfortunately, VIT will not be uploaded to the Tizen store then. I will, of course, still implement compatibility with mobile devices and I will also be uploading on app stores later on. As for now though, my current project is a smaller game. My current project is Vulcan. I got the name Vulcan from a race that's in Star Trek, which I'm sure any Star Trek fan is already aware of. It really doesn't have anything to do with Star Trek, I just couldn't find out a good name, so I decided to title it after something I really liked. Vulcan isn't really like any space shooter I've actually got the honor of seeing. Most space shooter follow the same guide lines and controls. There is actually only one game that plays similarly to Vulcan, and that's Asteroids. The only difference really is that Asteroids is very simple, and isn't a bunch of sprites. I'm actually going to be drawing most of the things in the game the same way that they did in Asteroids, though. Mainly because I like that look.
   I will tell you more when the game is complete, and until then I'll try to make as many updates as possible to the website. I made some updates today because I've got some free time, but I will be back in a couple days.

--- 11.5.2013
   Well, it's a new week, and as promised, I'm going to be updating my website again. It may not be a whole lot of updating, but I'm going to be doing my best with what I have to work with. My plan for this week is to add onto the Learn section of the website, as that's my primary goal as of right now. I want to start teaching you myself instead of directing you to websites. I'm going to eventually be sectioning things on the page off by categories such as: Begginers, Intermediate, Pro, Kiira. Kiira will be a list of tutorials and the like for those that need help in certain areas of programming and game design.
   I really hope I can help. :)

--- 10.29.2013
   Just added in a new part to Kiira for people wanting to learn to design games! Up there in the navigation selections you will find different things that I will be adding in to assist people in the making of different things that pertain to games, but can also be used for many other purposes. I love games, but I want to people to be as open minded as possible with anything they learn there, because I love seeing creativity and innovation and that's what it's all about. thinking outside of the box. :) I really hope that this helps people! Also, a fair warning, I may not be posting until another week, because of school. It was nice to be able to take the time to add in these small features so that I may be able to help anyone who needs it. Remember, if you need any help with ANYTHING or just wish to speak to me, Contact Me.

--- 10.28.2013
   Well, as you can all see, Kiira has definitely changed a lot, and it might actually seem as if I just took all the Javascript out... Well, let me tell you, I'm not going to be permanently taking it out. As of right now, I'm a bit busy with many projects that will take up a a lot of my time, and I'm sure that a lot of you don't really like the basic black on red on white, boring, color scheme. Don't worry, friends, I will be adding more in with due time. :) My work schedule is very tight, with little time that I can really fit in to add things to my website. 
   Also, I need to keep you all updated on the way that the resources are going to go on my website. There is a system I've decided to set up for everything on the site. Everything that I make, or someone on the team makes, that will be for a specific package hosted on here, will cost money... IF it's a special package. The difference between a special package and a normal package is that the special package was will have more time and work put into it. Instead of the average way I typically do it when I say, "Oh, I don't think this fits in my game well, let's give it to other game designers and see if they can use it." I would rather give everyone a chance to buy a package of things that has better quality to it, that are more thought out and useful. Maybe a package of things that could make up an entire game on it's own as long as you know how to design the game, ya know? 
   Well, right now I've been trying to expand my range of games and I know that by now, everyone has probably been quite tempted to click on the navigation buttons instead of reading anything on here. XD I wouldn't really be surprised. I mean, who could pass up as great of a name as those that I'd given those buttons? And then once you go on the game one you get nothing but my junk pile. So, that's why I've been trying to do something else with all this. :) I'm making an engine to create the games that go on the website. Something that everyone (including me) can go on and create a game. Then as soon as the game is made, it will go on to the games page. There will be two main categories: Kiira and Members. The Members games page is where all the games go from other people upon creation. At first it's going to kinda suck though, so I'm going to later on set it up so that the games can be scored and the best games will go on top. Now, remember, there's a lot of time before that engine will be released! :) I'll definitely post links to the games I make without that on the Games page though, so you won't miss out on my games.
   
-- A long, long time ago on a galaxy far, far away...
   Welcome, one and all, to the official Kiira webpage redesign, that is here to stay. For a couple months I've been working on the packages that will soon be re-uploaded to the resource section of the website, and I realized something... I'm having some major issues with the website right now. I've been very busy with work lately, but tonight is going to be the major overhaul that changes everything. So, I know I was going about the website all wrong to begin with, and I apologize to everyone who found my old website a real pain. Within my new training in programming, I've greatly exceeded my previous skills in designing websites, and I really wish that I had my own domain to work off of, so I wouldn't have to keep relying on Weebly. 

   Well, please ignore my little rant there. :) Kiira is up and running again, with some major tweaks to... Well, everything. I'm going to be changing things a lot around here, starting with the blank games section... What fun is that? Oh, and to all of those who were around to see the side panel on my website and got to see that I was working on a Kiira Game Editor, don't worry. I'm getting to that. Actually, I'm starting with WebGL. I'll explain WebGL in just a moment, but I wanted to tell everyone of the updates I'm going to be making. First, and foremost, Kiira, as it stands, is a name I've begun to give myself, as a single developer. Though, it seems that I've met one person in one of my classes that I can work with. So, the success rate of video games designed by Kiira... Will most likely skyrocket. My problem has always been the lack of assistance. I'm a programmer, not a composer, artist, or level designer. So, with his assistance, things with Kiira Games are going to get even better. Also, games are going to be uploaded soon... Very soon... Be excited if you're a platformer fan! 

   So, I just said I was going to tell you about WebGL, didn't I? Well, instead of wasting my time by writing a freaking book about it (because I can't ever shut up about something that excites me) how about you take a look for yourself? 

   Yes, that sweet looking puppy is going to be what the Kiira Game Editor is going to be crafted using... Enjoy. 
</text>
